// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'FOUR' ",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'FIVE' ",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "1",
      "5",
      "9",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'SIX' ",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "9",
      "2",
      "4",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'SEVEN' ",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'EIGHT' ",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "8",
      "2",
      "0",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'NINE' ",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "0",
      "9",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'ZERO' ",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "0",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'THREE'  ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'TWO' ",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Choose the correct number  'ONE' ",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "1"
    ]
  }
  
];
